Classes Collection UA039
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Classes, 1816 -- 2022; 1857 -- 2000; UA039.001; 32.45 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes; 10 Digital Object(s) Of the 10 digital objects in this series, 2 have extent information comprising 18 files.; 56.0 Megabytes Of the 10 digital objects in this series, 2 have extent information comprising 67.7 MB.
  - Classes of 1930-1939, 1926 -- 2008; UA039.001.009
    - Key Fob, 1930; UA039.001.078.00004 (Box 78)
      Date is approximate; Leather band with metal fob; Fob was 1930 in blue on a brown background and a raised Tufts seal. Donated by Harvey Albert Fenton, son of Melvin (Feinstein) Fenton, E30 (deceased 2000-07-25).
    - Pipe, 1930; UA039.001.078.00005 (Box 78)
      Pipe with letter "T" carved into the bowl. Donated by Harvey Albert Fenton, son of Melvin (Feinstein) Fenton, E30 (deceased 2000-07-25).
    - Class Ring, 1930; UA039.001.078.00006 (Box 78)
      Donated by Harvey Albert Fenton, son of Melvin (Feinstein) Fenton, E30 (deceased 2000-07-25).
    - Class of 1935 50th Reunion pin, 1985; UA039.001.078.00007 (Box 78)
      Donated by Donna H. Sandin.
    - Jackson Junior-Senior blazer, 1938; UA039.001.079.00001 (Box 79)
      Donated by Alice Hayden Melnick, class of 1938 during her 70th class reunion.
    - Photographs of Alice Melnick in blazer, 1938 -- 2008; UA039.001.079.00002 (Box 79)
      Donated by Alice Hayden Melnick, class of 1938 during her 70th class reunion. Also includes four photographs of Ms. Melnick in the blazer, added 2008-06-24.
    - Jackson College, class of 1931, UA039.001.080.00001 (Box Shared 38)
    - Tufts College and Jackson College reunion, class of 1931, UA039.001.080.00012 (Box Shared 38)
    - Reunion, men and women sitting at table, 1950 -- 1960; UA039.001.080.00015 (Box Shared 38)
      Appears to be the class of 1931, but is not certain. The dates are approximate.
    - Bachelor of science in electrical engineering awarded to Mazeppa Don Bells, Jr., Tufts College, 1931; UA039.001.080.00027 (Box Shared 38)
      This item was found uncataloged in the stacks in winter 2009. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials. Item donated by Jane Whitney on September 24, 2007, daughter of Mazeppa Don Betts, Jr.
    - Reunion, class of 1931, men and women sitting at table, 1950 -- 1960; UA039.001.080.00029 (Box Shared 38)
    - Dear Alma Mater, 1936; UA039.001.085.00001 (Box 85)
      Belonged to Helen Taylor (nee Dobbin). Donated by her children Stephen and Elizabeth Taylor.
    - Class Day booklet, 1936; UA039.001.085.00002 (Box 85)
    - Clippings, 1932 -- 1936; UA039.001.085.00003 (Box 85)
    - Jumbo Book, 1932 -- 1936; UA039.001.085.00004 (Box 85)
    - 25th Reunion, 1961; UA039.001.085.00005 (Box 85)
    - 30th Reunion, 1966; UA039.001.085.00006 (Box 85)
    - 35th Reunion, 1971; UA039.001.085.00007 (Box 85)
    - 40th Reunion, 1976; UA039.001.085.00008 (Box 85)
    - 45th Reunion, 1981; UA039.001.085.00009 (Box 85)
    - 50th Reunion, 1986; UA039.001.085.00010 (Box 85)
    - 55th Reunion, 1991; UA039.001.085.00011 (Box 85)
    - 70th Reunion, 2006; UA039.001.085.00012 (Box 85)
    - Photo Album, 1926 -- 1930; UA039.001.086.00001 (Box 86)
      Belonged to Herbert Gilmor. Donated by his son Chuck Gilmor. Dates are approximate.
    - Identification sheets for photo album, 1926 -- 1930; UA039.001.086.00002 (Box 86)
    - Class Day booklet, 1930; UA039.001.086.00003 (Box 86)
    - 25th Reunion materials for Class of 1930, 1955; UA039.001.086.00004 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 5)
    - 25th Reunion materials for Class of 1930, UA039.001.086.00005 (Box 86)
    - Melvin Thorner Class of 1935 memorabilia, 1933 -- 1935; UA039.001.086.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 85)
      This file contains Pen, Paint and Pretzels programs, a Class Day Program, a Commencement Program, an issue of the Tuftonian, and an issue of the Tufts Weekly.
      Gift of Susan Thorner, 2016, accession 2016.123.
    - Class of 1937 panoramic photograph, UA039.000505 (Box 72)
      Open for research. Fragile condition - please consult with archivist.
  - Classes of 1940-1949, 1940 -- 1995; UA039.001.010
    - Classes, 1940; UA039.001.009.00016 (Box 9)
      Program, Class Day; program, Junior weekend; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 50th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 65th reunion booklet, Tufts University, Class Song.
    - Classes, 1941; UA039.001.009.00017 (Box 9)
      Program, Class Day; program of Chapel Exercises, Class Day; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson.
    - Classes, 1941; UA039.001.009.00018 (Box 9)
      25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 25th reunion booklet, School of Dental Medicine; 50th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1942; UA039.001.009.00019 (Box 9)
      15th reunion booklet; Tufts Jackson; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 50th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; Class of 1942 directory.
    - Classes, 1942; UA039.001.009.00020 (Box 9)
      25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 30th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 45th reunion booklet. Also contains materials donated by Joseph Primack, A40 D42. These materials include a 1968 pamphlet, "Message to the Tufts Community" about social unrest on campus and in the world, a photograph of "Bill" at the 1966 Commencement ceremony, and two award letters for Dr. Primack, one electing him as a member of the Robert R. Andrews Honor Society in 1941, and another for interest and scholarship in dentistry from 1942.
    - Classes, 1943; UA039.001.009.00021 (Box 9)
      Program, Senior Banquet; 20th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 25th reunion report, School of Medicine; press bulletins; 15th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson.
    - Classes, 1943; UA039.001.009.00022 (Box 9)
      25the reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 50th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1944; UA039.001.009.00023 (Box 9)
      Photo, engineering class of 1944; 15th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 20th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 35th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 50th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 50th reunion bookle, School of Medicine; photo collage, 35th reunion; 40th reuinion booklet, School of Dental Medicine.
    - Classes, 1944; UA039.001.009.00024 (Box 9)
      25th reunion booklet, Tufts University; correspondence.
    - Classes, 1945; UA039.001.009.00026 (Box 9)
      Tufts University School of Medicine 25th Reunion booklet; Tufts/Jackson 35th & 40th Reunions, correspondence; World War II "Dropouts" list, correspondence
    - Classes, 1945; UA039.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
      25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 40th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1945; UA039.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
      50th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 40th reunion souvenir seal.
    - Classes, 1945; UA039.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
      50th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1945; UA039.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
      25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; correspondence.
    - Classes, 1946; UA039.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
      25th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 25th and 40th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1947; UA039.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
      25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts University; correspondence; 1947 Tufts calendar; 25th, 40th, 50th, and 55th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; class history and journal.
      55th reunion booklet transferred by Office of Alumni Relations, 2017, accession UA-2018-014
    - Classes, 1948; UA039.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
      Ivy Society booklet; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 40th and 50th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1949; UA039.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
      Program, Class Day; 35th reunion booklet, School of Dental Medicine; 10th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts University; news service releases; 40th and 50th reunion booklets, School of Medicine.
    - "Fifty Years Alumnus Tufts College" Pin, 1995; UA039.001.018.00007 (Box 18)
      Blue and Brown fabric attached to pin; features an image of Goddard Chapel, the Tufts College Seal, and "Fifty Years Alumnus Tufts College;" donated by Jason H. Samuels E'1945
    - Class of 1940 photographs, UA039.001.060.00005 (Box 60)
    - Class of 1941 photographs, UA039.001.060.00006 (Box 60)
    - Class of 1942 photographs, UA039.001.061.00001 (Box 61)
    - Class of 1943 photographs, UA039.001.061.00002 (Box 61)
    - Class of 1944 photographs, UA039.001.061.00003 (Box 61)
    - Class of 1944 photographs, UA039.001.061.00004 (Box 61)
    - Class of 1945 photographs, UA039.001.061.00005 (Box 61)
      - Class of 1945 photographs, UA039.001.061.00005.00001 (Box 61)
        Two photographs donated by Jason H. Samuels E'1945.
    - Class of 1946 photographs, UA039.001.061.00006 (Box 61)
    - Class of 1947 photographs, UA039.001.061.00007 (Box 61)
    - Class of 1948 photographs, UA039.001.062.00001 (Box 62)
    - Class of 1949 photographs, UA039.001.062.00002 (Box 62)
    - Classes, 1944, 25th Reunion Book, 1969; UA039.001.066.00001 (Box Volume 66)
    - Class of 1940 Fiftieth Reunion booklet, 1990; UA039.001.072.00005 (Box 72)
      Donated by Phillip Primack.
    - Beige Freshman Numeral Vest with Brown and Blue numbering for 1945, UA039.001.073.00005 (Box 73)
      Donated by Peter F. Merenda A'45; G'48. Merenda earned three numerals for cross country, indoor and outdoor track; but it is not known which sport this vest was awarded for.
    - Entire Tufts College, student body and faculty, 1941-11; UA039.001.080.00017 (Box Shared 38)
      Donated by Richard G. Woodward, class of 1944. Inscription on back of photo: "Richard G. Woodward, class of 1944. 2nd face down from outer left corner of chapel tower (actually graduated 1948 thanks to WWII)."
    - Class of 1940 25th Reunion stein, 1965; UA039.001.082.00001 (Box 82)
      Belonged to Joseph E. Primack. Donated by Philip Primack.
    - Class of 1941 panarama, UA039.001.087.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 3)
      photographic print; Roy D.Young Studio
    - Elinor Lyle Crouter Jackson College 1943 memorabilia, 1939 -- 1943; UA039.000501 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      Donated by Monica Azzolini, 2020, accession UA-2021-001.
      Newspaper clippings, telegram, photographs, Senior Banquet of the Class of 1943 Jackson College program, and handwritten and typed correspondence, including a handwritten letter on Student Council, Jackson College for Women letterhead welcoming Crouter to the college with advice about coming to campus.
  - Classes of 1950-1959, 1947 -- 2014; UA039.001.011
    - Classes, 1950; UA039.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
      10the reunion booklet, Tufts University; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts College; public relations releases; 45th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1951; UA039.001.010.00010 (Box 10)
      20th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 10th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 40th reunion booklet, School of Medicine, 50th reunion booklet; 60th reunion booklet.
      60th reunion booklet transferred by Office of Alumni Relations, 2017, accession UA-2018-014.
    - Classes, 1953; UA039.001.010.00011 (Box 10)
      45th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 10th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts University.
    - Classes, 1954; UA039.001.010.00012 (Box 10)
      Calendar,5th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 40th, 45th and 25th reunion booklets; School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1954; UA039.001.010.00013 (Box 10)
      Tufts Film Society invitation, "You Can't Take it With You"; 10the reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts Jackson; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; membership card TFS; songs.; 30th reunion, School of Dental Medicine.
    - Classes, 1955; UA039.001.010.00014 (Box 10)
      25th and 40th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 25th, 30th and 50th reunion booklet, Tufts University; program, Senior Dinner; calendar.
    - Classes, 1955; UA039.001.010.00015 (Box 10)
      50th reunion booklet; 1954 Five New Poets (Donated by Marcia Goldsmith); 1955 Jackson College Tuition Bill (Donated by Marcia Goldsmith), Tufts College Calendar for 1955 (Donated by Peter F. Merenda, A'45; G'48)
    - Classes, 1956; UA039.001.010.00016 (Box 10)
      Class giving record, Liberal Arts; Middle Hall English Club membership card; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; program, Senior Dinner; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; program, Junior Dinner and Dance; engagement calendar; Fletcher 50th Reunion Yearbook.
    - Classes, 1956; UA039.001.010.00017 (Box 10)
      Newsletter; 15th reunion booklet, directory; 20th reunion booklet, Tufts College.
    - Classes, 1959; UA039.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
      25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; Fifth reunion booklet, Tufts University; Tenth reunion booklet, Tufts University; Fifteenth reunion booklet, Tufts University; Freshman directory, 1955-56, class of 1959, 50th reunion booklet.
    - Class of 1950 photographs, UA039.001.062.00003 (Box 62)
    - Class of 1951 photographs, 1947; UA039.001.062.00004 (Box 62)
      - Members of the Class of 1951 at registration, 1947; UA039.001.062.00004.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 62)
        Students; Bow ties; Student registration; photographic print
    - Class of 1952 photographs, UA039.001.062.00005 (Box 62)
    - Class of 1953 photographs, UA039.001.062.00006 (Box 62)
    - Class of 1954 photographs, UA039.001.062.00007 (Box 62)
    - Class of 1955 photographs, UA039.001.062.00008 (Box 62)
    - Class of 1957 photographs, UA039.001.062.00009 (Box 62)
    - Class of 1958 photographs, UA039.001.063.00001 (Box 63)
    - Image of Tufts signed by class of 1958, UA039.001.063.00011 (Box 63)
      Framed image of Tufts, signed by the class of 1958. Front: Tufts University, Medford, Massachusetts. Back: Eglomise Designs, Inc., and signatures.
      photo frames
    - Class of 1959 - 5th reunion materials, 1964; UA039.001.064.00001 (Box 64)
    - Class of 1959 - 10th reunion materials, 1969; UA039.001.064.00002 (Box 64)
    - Class of 1959 - 15th reunion materials, 1974; UA039.001.064.00003 (Box 64)
    - Class of 1959 - 15th reunion booklets, 1974; UA039.001.064.00004 (Box 64)
    - Class of 1959 - 15th reunion completed questionnaires for booklets, 1974; UA039.001.064.00005 (Box 64)
    - Class of 1959 - 20th reunion materials, 1979; UA039.001.064.00006 (Box 64)
    - Classes, 1957; UA039.001.071.00001 (Box 71)
      5th reunion "Who Was There" booklet; program, Senior Dinner; 25th and 40th reunion booklets, School of Medicine; 25th reunion misc; 50th reunion booklet.
      50th reunion booklet transferred by Office of Alumni Relations, 2017, accession UA-2018-014
    - Classes, 1958; UA039.001.071.00002 (Box 71)
      Program, Alumni Day; comic strip "Life Upon the Muddy Mystic"; publication, "Cook's Tour";40th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1958; UA039.001.071.00003 (Box 71)
      25th reunion booklet and directory, School of Medicine; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts University; correspondence.
    - Classes, 1959; UA039.001.071.00004 (Box 71)
      Program, Class Day; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 30th reunion booklet, Tufts University.
    - Classes, 1959; UA039.001.071.00005 (Box 71)
      35th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 40th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; Desk calendar, 1959.
    - Tufts-Jackson, class of 1959, 10th reunion, 1969; UA039.001.080.00018 (Box Shared 38)
    - Vincent Mainiero, Class of 1953, personal material, 1949 -- 2014; UA039.000508
      Gift of Beth Mainiero in honor of Vincent A. Mainiero, 2020, accession MS-2021-002.
      This file contains recordings of several of Vincent Mainiero's mid-term exams, photographs, clippings, and a copy of "Jumbo: Marvel, Myth, Legend."
      - Mid-term recordings and "The Call of the Far-Away Hills" record, 1950 -- 1953; UA039.000509 (Box 87)
        Four 10" 78 rpm records, including three recorded by Mainiero as part of mid-term exams and one Japanese record Mainiero purchased while stationed in Hokkaido with the United States Army. The mid-term recordings relate to John Keats, Alfred Tennyson, Francis Bacon, Eugene Field, the abolition of slavery, and the need for a Tufts radio station.
      - Photographs, clippings, and "Jumbo: Marvel, Myth, and Mascot", circa 1950 -- 2014; UA039.000510 (Box Shared 151, Folder 1)
        Photographs of Tufts cheerleaders, fraternity and sorority pins, Mainiero's graduation day, and a Class of 1953 reunion; clippings from Tuftonia and Tufts Magazine; and a copy of the book "Jumbo: Marvel, Myth, Legend," by Andrew McClellan.
      - Photograph album and Alpha Sigma Phi class photos, 1949 -- 1953; UA039.000511 (Shared 150, Folder 2)
        Loose pages from a photograph album documenting the February 1950 Tufts College Winter Carnival and life on campus and class photos of the members of Alpha Sigma Phi in 1952 and 1953.
  - Classes of 1960-1969, 1960 -- 2017; UA039.001.012
    - Classes, 1960; UA039.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
      25th, 35th, 45th, 50th reunion booklet, Tufts University; program, Class Day; poem, Class day; profile of the entering class, Tufts and Jackson; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 25th reunion, School of Dental Medicine.
      45 and 50th reunion booklets transferred by Office of Alumni Relations, 2017, accession UA-2018-014
    - Classes, 1961; UA039.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
      25th reunion booklet, School of Dental Medicine; 10th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson; 25th reunion, School of Medicine; program, Senior Dinner; program, Class Day; Report to Schools on Admissions, 1958; Junior Dinner Dance dance card, 1960; ticket to The Weavers concert at Cousens Gym, 1960; 50th reunion booklet, Tufts University.
    - Classes, 1962; UA039.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
      25th reunion booklet, School of Dental Medicine; 25th and 35th reunion booklets, School of Medicine; 20th reunion booklet, Tufts University; Class of 1962 Newsletter for Tufts College and Jackson College; freshman directory; program, Senior Dinner; Bulletin of Tufts Crane Theological School, 1962.
    - Classes, part 1, 1963; UA039.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
      5th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 35th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; photos, class of 1963; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; program, Senior Dinner; 25th Jubilee reunion advert; Jackson and A and E profile of entering class
    - Classes, part 2, 1963; UA039.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
      25th reunion Alumni weekend booklet; 30th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; 25th reunion booklet, Dental School; 50th reunion booklet, Tufts University.
    - Classes, 1964; UA039.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
      See also box 72; 20th and 25th reunion booklet, School of Dental Medicine; register of students; freshman directory; 25th, 30th and 35th reunion booklets, School of Medicine; 5th and 20th reunion booklet, Tufts University; program "Capping Exercises", School of Dental Medicine; freshman newsletter, 1964; words and music to "Threshold of Greatness" by Bartlett and Clark
    - Classes, 1965; UA039.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
      25th and 30th reunion booklets, School of Medicine; 19th reunion booklet, Tufts University; Program, Senior Dinner; Bulletin of Tufts Crane Theological School.
    - Classes, 1966; UA039.001.011.00009 (Box 11)
      25th reunion booklet, School of Dental Medicine; Program, Senior Dinner; program, "Meet and Mix in '66"; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; Senior Class Album.
    - Classes, 1967; UA039.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
      Program, Class Day; 25th and 30th reunion booklets, School of Medicine; Senior Week Supplement; 5th reunion booklet, Tufts-Jackson, 40th reunion booklet; 50th reunion booklet.
      50th reunion booklet gift of Peter Karalekas, 2017, accession UA-2017-049.
    - Classes, part 1, 1968; UA039.001.011.00011 (Box 11)
      Program, Class Day; 25th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 1968 Senior Supplement; Tufts Alumni Review, Fall 1968.
    - Classes, part 2, 1968; UA039.001.011.00012 (Box 11)
      25th and 30th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; Freshman orientation materials donated by Tom Hart (2009.082).
    - Classes, part 1, 1969; UA039.001.011.00013 (Box 11)
      15th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 25th and 30th reunion booklets, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, part 2, 1969; UA039.001.011.00014 (Box 11)
      1969 register of students; address to the Tufts Jackson class of 1969; correspondence; 10th reunion booklet, Tufts University.
    - Class of 1960 photographs, UA039.001.063.00003 (Box 63)
    - Class of 1962 photographs, UA039.001.063.00004 (Box 63)
    - Class of 1963 photographs, UA039.001.063.00005 (Box 63)
    - Class of 1964 photographs, UA039.001.063.00006 (Box 63)
    - Class of 1965 photographs, UA039.001.063.00007 (Box 63)
    - Class of 1967 photographs, UA039.001.063.00008 (Box 63)
    - Beanie, Class of 1968, UA039.001.069.00001 (Box 69)
    - Class of 1968 beanie and Boy Scout Troop 429 neckerchief, 1965 -- 1968; UA039.001.069.00002; .2 Linear Feet (Box 69)
      This file contains one Class of 1968 freshman beanie, and one neckerchief of Boy Scout Troop 429, which was sponsored by Tufts through the Leonard Carmichael Society.
      Gift of J. David Naparstek, 2018, accession UA-2019-022.
    - Class of 1964 Senior Week and Commencement information, UA039.001.072.00004 (Box 72)
      From the estate of Brent Jackson.
    - Proclamation " Richard S. Brooks Fund of the Dental Class of 1963", UA039.001.080.00028 (Box 79)
      The proclamation of the Dental School class of 1963 was found uncataloged in the reading room in March 2009.
    - Classes, 1965; UA039.001.071.00006 (Box 71)
  - Classes of 1970-1979, 1970 -- 2014; UA039.001.013
    - Classes, 1970; UA039.001.011.00015 (Box 11)
      Freshman directory, 1970; 10th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; A case for a "non-traditional" graduation ceremony
    - Classes, 1971; UA039.001.011.00016 (Box 11)
      Program, Class Day; "A Brief Analysis of the American Council on Education Data Tufts University Freshman, Fall 1967".
    - Classes, 1972; UA039.001.011.00017 (Box 11)
      School of Medicine Class of 1972 newsletter #2; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1973; UA039.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
      Program, Class Day; "Survey of the Class of 1973, Jackson College"; correspondence; 25th reunion booklet, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1974; UA039.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
      1974 post graduation report; 10th reunion booklet, Tufts University; 20th and 25th reunion booklets, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1975; UA039.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
      Class of 1975 profile pamphlet; 20th reunion booklet, School of Medicine; correspondence.
    - Classes, 1976; UA039.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
      Class of 1976 profile pamphlet.
    - Classes, 1977; UA039.001.012.00005 (Box 12)
      Class of 1977 profile pamphlet; senior week activities calandar; 20th reunion, School of Medicine.
    - Classes, 1978; UA039.001.012.00006 (Box 12)
      Advert, Senior Week; 20th reunion booklet, School of medicine; correspondence.
    - Classes, 1979; UA039.001.012.00007 (Box 12)
      15th and 20th reunion booklets, School of Medicine; Tufts Class of 1979 profile.
    - Gwen Schneidkraut audio recording 1974, 2014; UA039.001.012.00029 (Box 12)